人人影視傾情奉獻
翻譯  妖精希亞
翻譯  國士章魚X
翻譯  ET外星人
翻譯  杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯  沫沫
翻譯  丶Charl
翻譯  癢癢惦記小跟班
時間軸  ans
顧問  老杜
后期  餓得慌
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第四季  第九集
肯塔基  你們有53票
Kentucky, you have 53 votes.
你們要投給誰
How do you cast them?
秘書長女士
Madam Secretary,
作為肯塔基州參議員
as a senator for the great Commonwealth of Kentucky,
我很榮幸以代表團的名義發言
I'm proud to speak on behalf of the delegation's chair.
肯塔基聯邦
The Commonwealth of Kentucky,
德比賽馬會之鄉  野貓隊之鄉
home of the Derby, the Wildcats,
波本酒的發源地
and the birthplace of bourbon,
在美國副總統提名投票上
for Vice President of the United States,
民主黨全國代表大會
副總統提名點名投票
將13票投給國務卿凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
casts 13 votes for Secretary of State Catherine Durant...
11票投給內華達州參議員約瑟夫·貝克
11 for Senator Joseph Baker of Nevada,
9票投給西弗吉尼亞州州長蘭道爾·史密斯
9 for Governor Randall Smith of West Virginia,
佛羅里達州州長吉爾·哈利
7 apiece for Governor Jill Haley of Florida
和加州議員莎倫·皮爾斯女士各7票
and Congresswoman Sharon Pierce of California,
5票投給我們路易斯維爾市長  吉爾·卡森
5 for one of our own, the Mayor of Louisville, Jill Carson...
還有1票投給美國第一夫人
and 1 vote for the First Lady of these United States,
克萊爾·安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Claire Underwood.
路易斯安那  你們共有61票
Louisiana, you have 61 votes.
你們都投給誰
How do you cast them?
很激動人心吧  可以感受到熱烈的氣氛
Isn't this exciting? You can feel the electricity.
好久沒舉辦過開放黨代會了
Been a very long time since an open convention.
我很意外您自己一票都沒有  參議員
I'm surprised you didn't get a few votes yourself, Senator.
斯考特·希爾參議員
肯塔基州  民主黨
我沒參選副總統
I'm not running for vice president.
克萊爾·安德伍德也沒有  她還是得了一票
Neither is Claire Underwood and she got one.
是我投的
That was my vote.
是想增加點趣味嗎  先生
Trying to throw some levity into the proceedings, sir?
才不是  我認為她能勝任副總統
Hell, no! I think she'd make a terrific vice president.
民主黨全國代表大會  亞特蘭大
安德伍德夫人  安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood! Mrs. Underwood!
我有幾個問題  安德伍德夫人  您有時間嗎
A couple of questions, Mrs. Underwood, if you have a moment?
可以  我只有幾分鐘
Yes, I only have time for a few.
歡迎來到亞特蘭大  安德伍德夫人
Welcome to Atlanta, Mrs. Underwood.
謝謝
Thank you.
您能對希爾參議員的投票發表評論嗎
Can you comment on Senator Sheer's vote?
我很榮幸  但我相信他是開玩笑的
Well, I am flattered. But it's all in good fun, I'm sure.
安德伍德夫人  他說他還會再為您投票
Mrs. Underwood, he says he'll vote for you again.
我鼓勵所有人  包括希爾參議員
Well, I am encouraging everyone, including Senator Sheer,
把票投給凱茜·杜蘭特
to vote for Cathy Durant.
總統和我
Both the president and I
都認為她是這個職位的最佳人選
think she is the best choice in the field.
你把我們寫的稿全改了
You changed everything we wrote.
那個稿子沒有創意  也不押韻
There was no imagination to it. No rhythm.
從他們就職就是我們在為他們寫講稿
We've been writing their speeches since they took office.
我們知道自己在做什么
We know what we're doing.
你們在意的是好講稿  還是撰稿人署名
Well, do you want it to be good, or do you want it to be yours?
最讓我激動的投票
The vote I'm most excited about
是昨天在眾議院
is the victory our
我們的《背景普查法案》取得的勝利
Background Check Legislation got in the House yesterday.
所以我希望參議院也能盡快向他們學習
So I'm hoping that the Senate will follow their lead soon,
這樣總統就能簽署這一法案
and that the president can sign it into law.
我得走了  非常感謝
I have to go. Thank you so much.
謝謝您邀請我們
Thank you... for inviting us.
不
No.
是我應該謝謝你和你兒子
It's me who has to thank you and your son.
他救了我的命
He saved my life.
雖然是因為那樣一場悲劇
No matter how tragic the circumstances.
我想帶你見見其他接受者
I want you to meet some of the other recipients.
這是詹姆斯
This is James...
他接受了你兒子的一個腎
who received one of your son's kidneys.
這是路易莎
And this is Luisa...
她接受了你兒子的心臟
who received your son's heart.
路易莎是名單上的第一個
Luisa was at the top of the list.
她本就剩幾小時的生命了
She was hours away from dying.
如果可以的話  我們一起拍個照吧
Uh, if we could, let's all get together for a photo.
詹姆斯  過來
James? Right here.
-你到這兒來  -好的
- You come right here. - Okay.
好了
All right.
這邊  很好
This way. Great.
總統對他的移植手術并不避諱
The president isn't shying away from, uh, his transplant.
我認為這是明智之舉
Well, I think it's a smart move.
既然不能否認  何必要隱瞞呢
You can't deny it, so why try to hide it?
另外  我認為這也強調了
Plus, I think it underscores the importance
副總統選舉的重要性
of the vice presidential situation.
等等  把捐贈者的媽媽拉出來  感覺像在作秀
Wait, rolling out the donor's mom? That feels a bit exploitative.
我...等等
I... Look, hold on.
有點同情心  那孩子剛剛飲彈自盡了
A little bit of compassion, the kid just shot himself.
而且是用一把手槍
And with a handgun, no less.
合法購買的  不要把重點轉移到槍上
Legally purchased. Let's not put this on the gun.
很抱歉  這一切
Look, I am sorry, all of this, the whole thing,
黨代會...都是制造戲劇效果
the convention... It's theatrics.
鬧起來吧
Hey, look, I... bring on the circus.
比四天的專題廣告片有趣多了
It's a lot more fun than some four-day infomercial.
我們來說說競選者吧
Let's talk about the contenders themselves.
足有十多個
There's almost a dozen of 'em.
-你能小點聲嗎  -...確實有機會的
- Can you, uh, lower that, please? - ...really have a chance.
杜蘭特是頭一個
Durant, first among 'em.
這才第一天  上午11點
It's 11:00 in the morning, day one,
收視率比《艾倫秀》還高
and they're beating Ellen.
網站的流量也少了
Less traffic on the website, too.
看視頻的人越來越少了
People aren't watching the videos as much.
這個賣了一百多萬份
This sold over a million copies.
是網上閱讀量的五倍
Five times that many read it online.
對  那是上個月  這是這個月
Yeah, well, that was last month. This is this month.
我們公開了一位重量級競選搭檔
We announce a stellar running mate.
他在哈里發國問題上重創了安德伍德
He eviscerates Underwood on ICO.
我們手里有兩個
We have not one, but two
《名利場》封面供波利跳推送
Vanity Fair covers that Pollyhop's pushing,
而你們卻在這里大找借口
and all you give me is excuses.
應該是我們的曝光率壓制他們的黨代會
The point was for us to drown out their convention,
而不是反過來  我們得把風頭奪回來
not the other way around. We need to steal the thunder back.
那就去風口奪風頭
So go where the thunder is.
兩年來  我一直近在咫尺
I've been one heartbeat away for almost two years.
我對這個已經沒興趣了
My heart's not in it anymore.
過了11月我就回佛蒙特去了
I'm going to head back to Vermont after November.
也許繼續教書
Maybe start teaching again.
那你支持誰呢
Who are you supporting, then?
公開說是凱茜·杜蘭特
On the record, Cathy Durant.
私下里呢
And off the record?
我不是很喜歡她
I'm not the biggest fan.
為什么
Why?
俄羅斯危機期間她沒幫上什么忙
She wasn't much help during the Russia crisis.
可是她和佩特羅夫達成了協議
She closed the deal with Petrov.
功勞的確是歸到她頭上了
She took credit for it, sure.
但她從始至終都在阻撓那份協議
But she fought the deal every step of the way.
如果不是克萊爾  根本就不可能成
Nothing would've happened if it weren't for Claire.
第一夫人
The First Lady?
是前大使
The former ambassador.
我們在堪薩斯的支持率更接近了  但還不夠
We're closer in Kansas, but still not close enough.
你去爭取眾議院票時
Did you speak to Jefferies
和杰弗瑞斯談過了嗎
when you were there for the House vote?
他正在向弗雷德·西姆斯施壓
He's leaning on Fred Simms.
如果西姆斯可以拉來兩三名代表
If Simms could deliver two or three delegates--
那就能拿下整個堪薩斯了
That could push Kansas over the edge.
我可以聯系烏麥克
I can call Womack.
他在那邊有幾個朋友
He's got some friends over the border.
-珀利怎么樣  -珀利
- What about Pawley? - Pawley?
沃思堡治安官珀利  是我爸的老朋友了
Sheriff Pawley in Fort Worth, old family friend of my dad's.
他和達拉斯的幾位超級代表關系很近
He's close with some superdelegates from Dallas.
可以拉他過來
Yes, he's on board.
真得喜歡那些治安官
Gotta love those sheriffs.
我們在路易斯安那就是那么做的
That's how we do in Louisiana.
恩萊特呢
What about Enright?
我和他約好了在凱悅喝咖啡
I'm meeting him for coffee at the Hyatt.
話說我該過去了  我可不想遲到
In fact, I better get going. I don't wanna be late.
如果我們能拿下弗吉尼亞
Now, if we could lock up Virginia--
就會向全國發出強勢的訊息
It would send a very big message.
接下來就是肯塔基
And then Kentucky next.
肯塔基可喜歡你了
He's got a big old crush on you.
那你最好趕緊上路
We better get you on a move.
恩萊特最討厭不守時了
Enright is a stickler for punctuality.
我挺開心的  我都忘了我多喜歡做黨鞭
You know, I'm having fun. I forgot how much I miss being whip.
鞭子你來抽  蜜糖我來喂
You whip 'em. I'll sweet talk 'em.
胡蘿卜加大棒最有效了
Nothing like leather and sugar.
先生
Sir?
希爾參議員
Senator Sheer.
參議員  你干得太漂亮了
Senator, you did a fine job.
我最好能拿到黃金時段
Yeah, I better get prime time,
而不是在垃圾時段發表講話
not one of these midmorning speeches.
周三晚上八點  我親自和帕特打招呼
Eight o'clock, Wednesday night. I called Patti myself.
你知道政客這個物種
Do you know the main thing that separates
和其他物種最大的區別是什么嗎
a politician from the rest of the species?
政客愿意淹死一窩小貓
A politician is the one who would drown a litter of kittens
來換十分鐘的黃金時段
for ten minutes of prime time.
杜蘭特國務卿  我是政治新聞網的總編
Secretary Durant. Editor in chief, Politico.
沒事的
It's all right.
亞當  你親自來做報道嗎
Adam, are you covering this yourself?
68年以來的第一次開放黨代會
First open one since '68.
不過這天夠潮的
It's humid as hell, though.
我剛來就渾身透濕了
I just got here and I'm already soaked.
不過往好處想
On the plus side,
我聽說這里的艷舞俱樂部全國頂尖
I hear they have the best strip clubs in the country.
我能問幾個問題嗎
Can I ask you a couple questions?
-我有點急事  -就幾個
- Well, I'm in a hurry. - Just a couple.
不能公開
Nothing on the record.
和我說說關于
Tell me about the rumors
你在勃蘭登堡和佩特羅夫談判的傳聞吧
regarding the deal you struck with Petrov in Brandenburg.
什么傳聞
What rumors?
是第一夫人談妥的協議  而不是你
That it was the First Lady who brokered the deal, not you.
那是團隊合作的成果  是誰告訴你的
It was a team effort. Who is your source?
我不能透露  你懂的
I can't. You know that.
實在抱歉  我沒有時間了
Well, I'm afraid that's all the time I've got.
行程順利  亞當
Have a good trip, Adam.
總統接見器官捐贈者家屬
總統今早和凱倫·威廉姆斯一起
The president was on site this morning for a press briefing
在特斯頓侯爵酒店召開了記者會
at the Truxton Marquis with Karen Williams,
凱倫的兒子丹尼爾·威廉姆斯
the mother of Daniel Williams,
是他所用肝臟的捐獻者
the organ donor who provided his liver.
一起出席的還有其他器官接受者
Alongside him were all of the donor organs' recipients.
威廉姆斯太太和每一位接受者進行了交談
Ms. Williams took time to speak with each recipient
是她已逝兒子的器官挽救了他們的生命
whose life was saved in the wake of her son's passing.
總統借此肅穆的場合
The president used this solemn event
表達了他對分享生命拯救他人健康
to express his gratitude for those who share their lives
和幸福的人的敬意
for the health and welfare of others,
無論是通過捐贈器官  還是工作
whether through organ donation or through their work.
安東尼·莫雷蒂基金
總統在接受器官移植后
The president's condition has improved dramatically
健康狀況大為好轉
since his organ donation.
他住院期間
The entire country was on edge
全國人民的心都懸在空中
throughout his time in the hospital.
安東尼·莫雷蒂紀念基金
16歲少年丹尼爾
Sixteen-year-old Daniel,
把安德伍德總統從健康危機中解救了出來
who saved President Underwood from his health crisis,
他離開了這個世界
left this world by
卻回饋了很多他并不知道自己會觸動的人
giving back to so many others he never expected to touch.
這樣永恒的禮物是不會被遺忘的
Lasting tributes like this will not be forgotten.
目前  每年都有超過12.2萬的男人
Currently, there are more than 122,000 men,
女人和小孩
women and children
在尋求器官移植
seeking an organ transplant each year,
最常見的需求是腎臟  肝臟和心臟
most common needs being the kidney, liver, and heart.
雖然這些年來  捐贈者的數量有所上升
And while the number of donors has increased over the years,
接受者在找到一個健康匹配的器官前
recipients are still in for a long, potentially fatal waiting period
仍要熬過一段漫長且可能致命的等待期
before a healthy, matching organ becomes available.
這類移植的等待者
Waiting lists for these types of transplants
能堅持從幾天到幾個月不等
can last from days to months on end.
雖然安德伍德總統因情況緊急
Although President Underwood's critical condition
而登上了捐贈名單榜首
pushed him to the top of the donor list,
但他能及時獲得捐贈仍然是很幸運的
he was fortunate to have received a donation in time.
很多重癥或急需的病人
Many status one, or most in-need patients
捐贈
并不能及時得到救命的移植
do not receive a transplant in time to save their lives.
田納西州  你們有77票
Tennessee! You have 77 votes.
你們要投給誰
How do you cast them?
志愿者州...
From the Volunteer State...
田納西州的別稱
總統馬上會接聽電話
the president will be with you in a moment.
在美國副總統提名投票上  將73票
...we cast 73 votes for vice president
投給凱瑟琳·杜蘭特國務卿
to Secretary Catherine Durant,
4票投給約瑟夫·貝克參議員
and four votes to Senator Joseph Baker.
-凱茜  -跟恩萊特的見面很順利
- Cathy! - The meeting with Enright went well.
我之后給他打了電話  他說被你折服了
I put a call into him afterwards. He said you charmed him.
-我們有多少票了  -949
- That puts us where? - Nine-forty-nine.
這輪投票還贏不了  但也拉近了差距
We won't make this ballot, but we're getting close.
下輪肯定行  我確定
Next one. I'm sure of it.
等我們拿到最終數字再談吧
Let's talk once we get the final numbers.
好的  再見
Will do. Bye.
德克薩斯州  你們有237票
Texas, you have 237 votes.
我今晚要打的電話名單呢
Do you have my call list for tonight?
你們要投給誰
How do you cast them?
秘書長女士  我是魯伊斯·特雷霍
Madam Secretary, my name is Ruiz Trejo.
好的  我在電梯里遇見喬瓦尼了
I see. Uh, I ran into Giovanni in the elevator.
你可以劃掉他
You can cross him off.
再劃掉米爾福德
And cross off Milford.
她說她到死都只會支持貝克
She said she's gonna back Baker till the bitter end.
我們把所有票都投給了我們本區人
We cast all of our votes to our native daughter,
第一夫人
the First Lady,
也是美國未來的副總統
and the future Vice President of the United States of America,
克萊爾·安德伍德
Claire Underwood.
謝謝  德州  謝...
Thank you, Texas. And thank...
全部237票嗎  太好了
All 237? Nice.
我母親狠狠敲打了猶豫不定的
My mother brought the hammer down on the holdouts.
我剛發了奧斯丁和休斯頓的捐贈者名單給你
I just emailed you my donor lists for Austin and Houston.
應該至少能拿到兩百萬
Should be at least two million in the bank.
-瓊斯女士  -太好了
- Ms. Jones. - Oh, that's great.
我得掛了  記者來了
Oh, I gotta go. The cameras are here.
瓊斯女士  整個州都投給第一夫人
Ms. Jones, the entire state for the First Lady.
您如何評價呢
Will you comment?
我認為我們一致的選票就是你想要的評論
I think our unanimous vote is all the commentary you need.
總統在國情咨文中
Now, the president endorsed your race, uh,
背書了您競選接替您母親
your mother's vacant seat, uh, during the State of the Union.
是的  作為領跑者我很驕傲
He sure did, and I'm proud to be the front-runner.
這背書會不會跟您
Did that endorsement have anything to do
對第一夫人的支持有關呢
with your support of the First Lady?
我不否認安德伍德夫婦對我很好
Look, I won't deny that the Underwoods have been good to me.
但不是的  他們叫我投給凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
But no. They asked me to vote for Catherine Durant. And
雖然我認為杜蘭特國務卿
while I think Secretary Durant
會是這項工作的好人選
would be a wonderful woman for the job,
但我覺得克萊爾是最好的人選
I think Claire is the best woman for the job.
我真的很感激  戴安
Well, I really appreciate it, Diane,
我知道凱茜也會很感激的
and I know Cathy will as well.
好吧  再聯絡
All right, we'll speak soon.
新草稿
New draft.
莉安讓我再改改一些用詞...
LeAnn wanted me to work in some phrases...
和一些關鍵強調詞
and keyword amplifiers.
我只求你打個電話
All I'm asking is that you make the call.
如果是你說  他會聽的
He'll listen if it comes from you.
好生硬
It seems very clunky.
我同意
I agree.
能不能...
Is there a way to...
寫出她想要的但寫得...
put in what she wants and make it...
-更優雅一點  -他還在為
- more elegant? - He's still pissed about
我擔任黨鞭時否決的沒用國防法案生氣
that limp-dick defense bill I killed when I was whip...
也許吧...但我有我的限制
Maybe... but I have my limitations.
我覺得你不太相信她的分析
Well, you don't have much faith in her analytics, I don't think.
都是用數字在說話
It's paint by numbers.
是啊  她還說
Yes, well, she also says
你一直在疏遠其他講稿撰寫人
that you've been alienating some of the other speechwriters.
他們的平庸才是他們被疏遠的原因
Eh, well, their mediocrity is what's alienating them.
我對那個過敏
I'm allergic to it.
-我獨自工作更好  -讓我跟布賴斯談談
- I work better alone. - Let me speak to Bryce
看看我能做點什么
and then see what I can do.
沒錯  讓韋斯特電子來做
That's right. WestCAM should do it.
最好是今晚
Well, tonight if you can.
實在不行就早上...
The morning is fine if you can't...
我得走了  晚點再討論講稿吧
I have to go. Let's discuss the speech later.
對  我只需要你們州再來三票
Yeah, all I need is just three more from your state
我們就贏了
and we've got it.
對  就再多幾票
Yes, just a... just a few more.
三票
Like, three.
對  我也是  我們明天再聊
Yes, and so do I. I'll talk to you tomorrow.
晚安
Good night.
湯姆
Tom.
你來之后  我們都沒時間
I feel like we haven't even had a chance to say hello
打個招呼
since you came on board.
你是個大忙人
You're a busy man.
我從來沒閑下來過
I don't know the opposite.
也有好處  比如睡眠
It has its upsides. Like sleep.
還有朋友
And friends.
那個怎么樣了
How's the, uh...
要不是得吃藥
You know, if it weren't for the pills,
我一整天都不會想到這事
I could go through entire days without even thinking about it.
不知道那孩子如果知道
I wonder what that kid would think...
他成了總統身體的一部分會怎么想
if he knew that part of him was inside of the president's body.
真悲劇啊
Tragic, huh?
但話又說回來
But, then again,
一個人的悲劇是另一個人的寶藏
one man's tragedy is another man's treasure,
-是不是  -垃圾
- isn't that right? - Trash.
什么
What?
"一個人的垃圾"  應該這么說
"One man's trash." That's how the saying goes.
對了
Oh, right.
講稿怎么樣了
How's the speech coming?
這是你提名演講的先導講話  但...
Well, this is for the introduction to your acceptance speech, but...
不該是她自己的提名演講嗎
shouldn't it be for her own acceptance?
你想讓克萊爾贏  而不是杜蘭特
You want Claire to win, not Durant.
第一夫人當...
A First Lady as the...
真荒唐
That's ludicrous.
我不這么認為
I don't think so.
而且我覺得你也不
And I don't think you do either.
也許我錯了
Maybe I'm wrong.
但如果我說得對
But if I'm right...
她會需要一份終結者性的講稿
she's gonna need the speech to end all speeches.
提前讓我有準備會比較好
And it would be good for me to know that.
我還有其他事
I have some more work to do.
州長  你好嗎
Governor! How are you?
對  我也希望我在俄勒岡州
Yeah, well, I wish I was in Oregon, too,
但我現在在亞特蘭大
but I'm here in Atlanta
這里比站街女的屄還濕熱
where it's muggier than a street hooker's twat.
能和國務卿杜蘭特以及
I am honored to be mentioned
貝克參議員相提并論  我倍感榮幸
with Secretary Durant and Senator Baker.
他們都是經驗豐富的政治家
They're seasoned politicians.
但我已經有工作了
But I already have a job,
美國的第一夫人
First Lady of the United States.
德州的選票占比超過5%
Well, Texas is over 5% of the vote.
也是我的家鄉  所以別想得太多了
And my home state, so let's not make more of it than it is.
克萊爾
Claire!
祝賀你  你現在已經是第五名了
Congratulations. I think you're in fifth place now.
對  而你是當之無愧的第一
Yeah, with you in first, where you should be.
杜蘭特國務卿  您認為第一夫人有機會嗎
Secretary Durant, do you think the First Lady has a shot?
我覺得德州給了她一次機會
I think Texas just gave her one.
不開玩笑
Kidding aside, do you think
您認為她有外交經驗嗎
she has the foreign policy experience?
這無關緊要  就像我今早說的
It's beside the point. And like I said this morning,
我鼓勵所有人  也包括德州人
I encourage everyone, including Texas,
給杜蘭特國務卿投票
to vote for Secretary Durant.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood--
失陪一下
You know what, if you'll excuse me,
我想繼續去打電話
I want to get back to the phones,
確保凱茜得到提名
make sure Cathy gets this nomination.
-謝謝  -能單獨說句話嗎
- Thank you. - May I have a moment?
當然
Oh, of course.
有沒有人問過你勃蘭登堡的事
Did anyone ask you about Brandenburg
或者問過你的手下  打探你在其中的角色
or any of your people and your involvement there?
勃蘭登堡
Brandenburg?
沒有  我們不是都解決了
No, we put that to bed.
我之前也這么以為
That's what I thought,
所以亞當·古爾德告訴我
which is why I was surprised when Adam Gould told me
知情人說功勞全是你的時  我很驚訝
that he had sources saying you deserved all the credit.
我們都統一了說法
We all agreed to what our version of the story is,
這么說有人不聽話了
so somebody isn't toeing the line.
肯定不是白宮的工作人員
Well, I'm sure it's not White House staff.
他肯定只是在瞎猜  想挑撥對立
I bet he's just fishing, trying to start some rivalry.
那樣就好了  如果他問你或者其他人
Well, I'd be grateful, if he asks you, or anyone else--
當然  而且我一直堅持我們的說法
Of course. And I've been sticking to our story...
是你讓俄羅斯人做出讓步
which it was you that got the Russians to back down,
我到那兒只是去支持你
and I was just there to support you.
代表們如果知道不會滿意的
That wouldn't look good to the delegates,
是你單獨和佩特羅夫見了面
the fact that you met with Petrov without me.
會看上去像我根本沒控制住...
It would look like I wasn't in command of--
我們討論的內容不需要讓人知道
No one needs to know what we discussed.
你沒什么可擔心的  凱茜  真的
You have nothing to worry about, Cathy. Honestly.
對  我可以幫你接通
Well, yeah. I can get you on the phone
農業部長的電話
with the Secretary of Agriculture,
但如果你想抗旱救災
but if you want drought relief,
那只有史蒂文斯和洛佩茲可遠遠不夠
I'm gonna need more than just Stevens and Lopez.
貝克那邊有什么安排嗎
Has anything been set up with Baker yet?
明早在他的房里
Tomorrow morning, in his room.
這卡得也太緊了
Well, that's cutting it close.
他今晚還要和
He's at a big dinner with
佛羅里達國會代表團吃飯
the Florida congressional delegation tonight.
那好  請務必回電
Well, all right, and call me back.
凱茜已經聽見風聲了
The rumors have gotten to Cathy.
我們本來就是想把風聲傳出去
Well, we did want them to spread. That was the idea.
我們得有人找她談談
I think one of us needs to speak with her.
但計劃是要等到萬不得已再去
Yeah, but the plan was to wait till it was inevitable.
如果我們不盡快把她拉進來  弗蘭西斯
If we don't involve her sooner than later, Francis,
她可能會背叛我們
she could turn on us.
那好  你去見貝克
All right, you take your meeting with Baker.
-我去和凱茜談  你去安排  -好  先生
- I'll talk to Cathy. You set that up. - Yes, sir.
你打算說到什么地步
How much are you going to say?
讓她有心理準備就行
Just enough to prepare her.
不少人來電問安德伍德夫人和俄羅斯的事
A lot of calls about Mrs. Underwood in Russia.
你否認了
Denying?
我無視了  基本上就是等于默認了
Ignoring, which is the same as confirming.
-很好  -克萊爾在里面嗎
- Good. - Claire in there?
她正在和總統私談
She's speaking privately with the president.
我進去她不會介意的
Oh, I'm sure she won't mind.
查莉安查得怎么樣了
Where are we with LeAnn?
-她沒有問題  -不可能
- She's clean. - No.
我不相信
I refuse to believe that.
道格  如果我們的競選經理完蛋了
Doug, if our campaign manager bites the dust,
這對我們沒有好處
that hurts us.
這是我給你的任務
I gave you a task.
我繼續查
And I'll keep at it.
今早捐肝的新聞做得漂亮
Nice coverage on the liver thing this morning.
我給你發了些鏈接
I emailed you some links.
孩子們都大了  結婚了
Boys are older now, both married.
第三個孫子也要出世了
Got a third grandkid on the way.
如今我們不怎么去湖邊了
We don't get out to the lake much these days.
混首都圈代價不小啊
Washington takes its toll.
那是自然
It sure does.
我這些年犧牲了不少  安德伍德夫人
I've made a lot of sacrifices over the years, Mrs. Underwood.
最主要的就是沒時間陪孩子
Time with my boys, that's a big one.
我不知道能不能贏  但我參與進來了
Who knows if I'll win, but I'm in the mix.
我不能犧牲這次機會
And I can't sacrifice this opportunity
為凱茜·杜蘭特鋪路
to pave the way for Cathy Durant.
你贏不了的  參議員  你我都清楚
You won't win, Senator. We both know that.
可我不能幫她
But I can't help her.
我知道你們兩個有分歧
Now, I realize you two don't get along.
她看不慣我
She despises me.
老實說  我對她也是一樣
And I have to say, the feeling is mutual.
-聽著  -她一就任國務卿
- Well, listen-- - The moment she became Secretary of State,
就讓共和黨人
she got the Republicans to
把我從外事委員會趕出來了
remove me from the Foreign Relations Committee.
弗蘭西斯對此很不高興
And Francis was very upset about that.
可這都是過去的事了
But that was the past.
我們還是放眼未來吧
Let's talk about the future.
黨內對克萊爾如此支持  我們都沒想到
This support for Claire, it's caught us both off guard.
但我要你來做副總統
But you are my choice for vice president.
這一點不會變
Nothing has changed on that front.
我只是擔心那些傳言
Well, my only concern are the rumors.
的確會威脅我的勝算
They could damage my chances.
對  我們會想辦法應對的
Yes. And we'll do what we can to combat those.
克萊爾也是這么說的  我很感激
That's what Claire said, too, and it's much appreciated.
但是如果  僅僅是如果
But, if, and-- Oh, God, it's a big if.
但是如果
But what if...
對克萊爾的支持成了氣候
support for Claire picks up steam...
你不是真以為有這可能吧
Well, you don't actually think that will happen?
當然不了  第一夫人哪能當副總統
Oh, no. I mean, a First Lady as VP?
怎么行
No.
黨內想要個有經驗的人  人民也是
The party wants someone with experience, and so does the country.
那是當然
Absolutely.
但這次是開放黨代會
But... it is an open convention,
所以我們必須
and so we have to operate
準備應對一切可能發生的情況
with the belief that anything could happen.
媒體是對這個想法十分感興趣
I mean, the press is certainly enjoying imagining it.
那可不  這種頭條吸引眼球
Well, sure. It makes for a good story.
而這種新聞我們也沒辦法控制
Yeah, and it's the kind of coverage that we can't really control.
我是說
You know, I mean,
這種風聲會自己落地生根
these things have a way of taking on a life of their own.
就像佐伊·巴恩斯的報道
Like the Zoe Barnes story
影響了我擔任國務卿的提名
did about my nomination for Secretary of State.
只不過那是我們設計好的
Except that one we planted.
-這次你沒有嗎  -當然沒有
- And this one you didn't. - No, absolutely not!
克萊爾都不知道怎么回應這些支持票
I mean, Claire was mortified by those votes.
你是說  如果新聞報道影響了足夠多的人
What you're saying is if the coverage influences enough people...
我們必須有所準備
Well, we have to be prepared for that.
當然了
I mean...
從政治角度講  這簡直是災難
of course, politically, it would be a disaster.
也許是  也許不是
Maybe, maybe not.
你覺得不一定嗎
You don't think so?
我個人覺得克萊爾會非常稱職
Well, personally, I think Claire would do an excellent job.
你這么說我實在是沒想到
Well, I am very surprised to hear you say that.
你不相信她會嗎
You don't believe she would?
我只是從來沒這么想過
Well, I've just never really considered it.
第一夫人  當副總統
The First Lady? As vice president?
有251個黨代表支持這個想法
Well, 251 delegates think it's a good idea.
他們大多來自德州  那只是玩笑
Well, most of those were from Texas, which was a lark.
是嗎
Was it?
支持我的黨代表不比你少  參議員
I have as many delegates as you do, Senator.
-但如果你開始支持我  -你得票翻倍
- But if you start pushing yours my way... - You double.
并且票數最多
And take the lead.
-然后凱茜再支持你獲得提名  -就是這樣
- And then Cathy puts you over the top. - That's the idea.
她也支持你嗎
So she's in on this?
她會的
She will be.
假設克萊爾真的票數領先
Well, let's say Claire does take the lead,
先不管可能性有多大吧
however unlikely that may be...
-我看基本不可能  -先假設她領先了
- Very unlikely, I would say. - Well, let's say she does.
你打算怎么辦
What do you propose?
我還真不知道
I honestly don't know.
你肯定得支持她吧
Well, you'd have to support her, wouldn't you?
你總不能拋棄自己的妻子
You can't abandon your own wife.
那倒是  可我也不能拋棄你啊
Uh, true, but I can't abandon you either.
如果她真的領先了
Well, if she took the lead,
我想我也得支持她了
I suppose I'd have to support her, too.
我決不會要求你做那樣的事
No, I would never ask you to do that.
你不必要求我  我們是一邊的
But you don't have to ask. We're on the same team here.
那我就直接問了
Well, to be perfectly blunt...
我有什么好處
what's in it for me?
你想要什么好處
What would it take?
來推銷的是你  你說說吧
You're doing the selling. Make me an offer.
假設克萊爾成功了
Let's say Claire gets it.
如果你贏了的話  我可以留任吧
I assume I stay on, if you get the general.
那肯定
Oh, absolutely.
我可不敢想像
I cannot imagine the next
接下來的四年里沒有你來當美國的...
four years without you being my Secretary of...
國務卿
...State.
你要把凱茜的工作給我
You'd give me Cathy's job?
我們是這么打算的
We're prepared to.
-道格  -國務卿女士
- Doug. - Madam Secretary.
出了個問題  先生
We have an issue, sir.
當我最早警告總統哈里發國會不斷壯大
When I first warned the president that ICO would grow,
并迅速擴張時  他什么都沒做
and grow quickly, he did nothing.
昨天哈里發國的領袖發了這條推特
Yesterday, the leaders of ICO sent out this tweet.
康威和布洛哈特在亞特蘭大
"蘇瓦爾已被我們奪下
"As Suwar is ours.
幼發拉底河將被鮮血染紅"
Soon heads will roll into the Euphrates."
不僅用阿拉伯文發  還有英語
That wasn't just in Arabic, that was in English,
以及其他16種語言
and sent out in 16 other languages.
他們善于媒體攻勢  在全球范圍內招募人手
They're media savvy, they're recruiting around the globe.
他們現在資金和人手都很充足
They have the money and the manpower now.
一旦他們進入幼發拉底河流域
Once they get to the Euphrates,
他們將扼住北敘利亞的命門
they'll have a choke hold on northern Syria.
我們必須采取行動  總統先生  馬上行動
We must act, Mr. President, and we must act now.
一般來說  黨代會有種
Normally, there's a tradition of sportsmanship
傳統的競爭精神
when it comes to conventions.
一名候選人保持低調
One candidate lays low
讓另一名候選人得到最大關注
so the other gets his or her moment in the spotlight.
但是總統不僅
But not only is the president
在無視一個重大的世界安全威脅
ignoring a great threat to the world's security,
他還侮辱了唯一站出來為我們大聲疾呼的人
he's insulted the one man who stood up and spoke out for us all.
這篇詳細闡述了
When this profile came out
將軍剛剛所說的內容的專訪發行后
about everything the general just mentioned,
白宮竟然指責他利用恐怖主義做政治文章
the White House said that he was politicizing terrorism.
而當我宣布布洛哈特將軍
And when I announced that General Brockhart
將成為我的競選搭檔后
was going to be my running mate,
總統競選團隊竟稱  我原話引用
the president's campaign said, and I quote,
"為將軍拿愛國換仕途的行徑感到惋惜"
"It's a shame the general traded in patriotism for careerism."
這可實在是稱不上競爭精神
Now, I don't call that very sportsmanlike.
這就是下作
I call it disgraceful.
總統為這個國家打過幾場仗
How many wars has the president fought for his country?
我們都知道  一次都沒有
I think we all know, none.
而他卻質疑這位曾多次為國而戰的人的愛國心
And he questions the patriotism of a man who has fought in many?
你聽好  總統先生
You hear me, Mr. President.
我要求你對哈里發國采取措施
I demand that you do something about ICO.
我要求你對將軍道歉
And I demand that you make an apology to the general.
你不做到這兩點  我們就不離開亞特蘭大
And we're not leaving Atlanta until you've done both.
各大電視臺都在直播
Live on every network right now.
他這步棋我服氣
I gotta hand it to him.
不知道是不是他自己的主意
I wonder if this was his idea,
因為都有點我的風格了
'cause it's almost something like I would do.
不管他  外面35度呢  讓他熬下去吧
We ignore him. It's 95 degrees. Let him sweat it out.
我們越是不理他  他得到的關注就會越高
I think the longer we ignore him, the more attention they'll get.
我同意莉安
I agree with LeAnn.
那就道歉吧
So apologize.
無非是面子而已
It's only pride.
如果您同意  我可以來道歉  先生
I can do it if you want, sir.
是我寫的聲明
I wrote the statement.
不  只有弗蘭西斯親自出面才管用
No, it only works if it comes from Francis.
克萊爾說得對
Claire's right.
除了道歉  我們還可以做更多
And we can do more than just apologize.
我可以和這混蛋見面
I can meet with the bastard.
州長和將軍指出的問題都非常重要
The issues the governor and the general raise are important ones.
這超越兩黨分歧  甚至超越政治
They transcend party affiliations and, quite frankly, politics.
鑒于此  我在此邀請州長
And so in that spirit, I'm inviting the governor
來這里和我見面
to come here and join me,
這樣我們可以舉行閉門會談  因為
so that we can have a conversation privately because...
無論最終誰當選  都要對付哈里發國
whoever becomes the president is going to have to deal with ICO
以及我們在世界各地面臨的其他恐怖威脅
and all of the other terrorist threats that we face around the globe.
所以我期待聽到
So I'm looking forward to hearing
他們可能有的任何想法和方案
whatever ideas and solutions that they may have...
因為聰明的總統會偷任何人的好主意
because a smart president will steal good ideas from anyone.
我們用仁慈干掉他們吧
Let's kill them with kindness, shall we?
-州長  -總統先生
- Governor. - Mr. President.
請讓將軍接一下電話好嗎
Would you please put the General on the line?
先生
Sir?
將軍
General...
你對這個國家的貢獻深受看重
your service to this country is greatly valued
你的愛國精神也是不容置疑的
and your patriotism is without doubt.
在激烈的競選之中  我們過火了
And in the heat of the campaign, well, we went too far.
我們發表了不該發表的聲明
We issued statements that we shouldn't have,
為此我要向你道歉
and for that I want to apologize,
希望你能接受
and I do hope that you will accept it.
對我而言  除掉哈里發國
Far more important to me than an apology
遠比道歉重要  總統先生
is eliminating ICO, Mr. President.
我非常贊同  將軍
I couldn't agree with your more, General.
麻煩你把電話交回給州長
If you'd be so kind as to put the Governor back on the phone.
我收到你的邀請了  總統先生
I received your invitation, Mr. President.
那你會來嗎  州長
And will you join us, Governor?
得是為了行動  而不是空談才行
Only if it leads to real action, not just talk.
我向你保證  州長
I can promise you, Governor,
也向整個美國保證  不會是空談
and the rest of America that it will not just be talk.
那好  如果真有助于保衛自由的話
Then, yes. If it truly leads to securing our freedom.
非常感謝  我期待與你見面
Thank you very much. I look forward to seeing you.
感謝大家
Thank you all very much.
這邊請  州長
Right this way, Governor.
你覺得這樣好嗎
Do you think this a good idea?
我還有什么選擇  他接我的招了
What choice do I have? He called my bluff.
歡迎  州長
Welcome, Governor.
謝謝  總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
我安排了一個房間
I have a room set up for us.
來
Here.
吃些午餐
Have some lunch.
我們有火腿  還有些火雞
We've got ham, and I think some turkey.
不用了  謝謝
I'm good, but thanks.
真的嗎
Really?
看你演的那一出  我以為你喜歡火腿[演過頭]呢
After the stunt you just pulled, I would've thought you love ham.
你特意放在這里的
You put this here on purpose.
一點讀物
Well, a little reading material, you know.
作為消遣
Something to pass the time.
我剛收到本·格蘭特的短信
I just got a text from Ben Grant
說我們來這里后
saying searches for this issue is
對這一期的搜索量爆表
going through the roof since we showed up here.
名利場
康威夫婦
本·格蘭特是波利跳的老板
Ben Grant owns Pollyhop...
沒錯
That's right.
而他又是你的人
And you own Ben Grant.
這不就是權力嗎  你能攬到的人
Isn't that what power is? The people you collect?
你那網絡直播真是害慘我了
You really screwed me with that webcast.
我本來把一切都安排好了
I had everything all planned out.
聯邦選舉委員會  司法部
The Federal Election Commission, the Department of Justice.
我就等著看你灰飛煙滅呢
I was looking forward to watching you go down in flames...
甚至鋃鐺入獄
maybe even behind bars.
抱歉讓你掃興了
Well, I'm sorry I ruined your fun.
不過挺難堪的  不是嗎
It's a bit embarrassing, though, isn't it?
把你們最親密的鏡頭公之于眾
I mean, sharing all your most intimate moments?
你孩子們的影像
Videos of your children?
我為我的家庭驕傲  怎么會難堪呢
I'm proud of my family. Why would I be embarrassed?
為了贏得所有人的喜愛  要屈尊至此
Well, just that you have to stoop so low to win everyone's love.
看起來挺絕望的  不是嗎
It feels a bit desperate, doesn't it?
你在所有民調中都落后15個百分點
You're 15 points behind in every poll.
絕望的人應該是你
So, if anyone's desperate, it should be you.
做總統的關鍵
Well, the key to being President
不只在于贏得勝利
is not only winning your battles,
而是要贏得有尊嚴
it's winning them with dignity.
我們談不談哈里發國了
Should we talk about ICO?
老天  我們為什么要談那個呢
Oh, God. Why would we want to do that?
這是我們會面的原因
It's why we're meeting.
對了
Oh, right.
"真正的談話  真正的行動"
"Real talk, real action."
那就是你關注的  是嗎
That's what you're all about, isn't it?
如果你想談  我們可以談  不過
Well, I suppose we could if you want to, but...
我們也可以把這一切暫時放下
then again we could just take a break from it all
放松一下
and relax a bit.
老天
God.
這火雞一股橡膠味
This turkey tastes like rubber.
總比真的吃橡膠[安全套]要好
Well, it's better than eating a real one.
我被民主黨人吹簫時
Oh, I always wear protection
總是要做好保護措施
when I'm getting my dick sucked by the Democrats.
你沒事吧
You okay?
沒事  沒事
I'm fine. I'm fine.
我吃東西時別和我開玩笑  我差點噎死
Don't make me laugh when I'm eating. I nearly choked to death.
那倒是讓我當上總統的一個辦法
Well, that is one way for me to become president.
-給  -謝謝
- Here you go. - Thank you.
-你還好吧  -嗯
- You okay? - Oh, yeah.
你介意我脫掉嗎
Do you mind if I take these off?
是嶄新的鞋  還沒磨合好呢
They're brand new and I'm still breaking 'em in.
你喜歡玩電子游戲  對吧
You like to play video games, right?
你從哪聽說的
Now, how did you hear about that?
湯姆·耶茨
Tom Yates.
對了
Oh, yes.
湯姆·耶茨
Tom Yates.
這個人你沒能攬到  是不是
That's one person you weren't able to collect, were you?
你是怎么把他招回來的
What did you do to get him back?
他肯定動過心的
Oh, look, I'm sure he was tempted.
畢竟他是個寫小說的
He is a fiction writer, after all.
而你是個紐約的共和黨人
You're a New York Republican.
這種虛構劇情很誘人啊  是吧
That's an attractive fiction, isn't it?
你是個來自南卡羅萊納的民主黨
And you're a Democrat from South Carolina,
這更像虛構的情節
that's even bigger fiction.
你說對了
Well, there you go.
而且我是個紐約的共和黨  基本上就是民主黨
And I'm a New York Republican, which is basically a Democrat.
如果你是民主黨人  那沒有人可以阻擋你
If you were a Democrat, you'd be unstoppable.
你絕對是新一代肯尼迪
You'd be the new JFK.
如果你是共和黨  那你會是誰  尼克松嗎
And if you were a Republican, who'd you be? Nixon?
尼克松可是個高效得多的總統
Nixon was a far more effective president.
人們崇拜肯尼迪只是因為他被爆頭了
The only reason people glorify Kennedy is because he got shot.
你不是也挨了一槍嗎
Well, you've got that going for you, too, now, don't you?
而你有你的搜索引擎
And you've got your search engine
和你的家庭視頻
and all your little home videos.
如果人們想了解你
See, if people want a piece of you...
你就滿足他們  對不對
you give it to them, right?
這就是人們想要的嗎
Oh, is that what people want?
了解你
A piece of you?
你玩電子游戲嗎
Do you play video games?
不  但我孩子玩
No. My kids do.
我兒子查理特別愛玩一個游戲
There's this one game that my son Charlie, he loves to play.
名字叫"細胞吞噬"
It's called Agar.Io.
我得承認我自己時不時也玩一玩
I have to admit, I might have played it a couple of times myself.
你一開始只是一個小點
You start out as a little dot.
然后你四處移動
And then you go around
吞噬其他的點  你就會變大
eating these other dots and you get bigger.
你變得越大
And the bigger you get,
就越得小心別被其他玩家更大的點吃掉
you gotta avoid getting eaten by the bigger players.
與此同時你還要繼續吞噬比你小的點
Meanwhile, you're trying to eat the smaller players.
聽著挺像總統競選的
Sounds a little like running for president.
那么現在和你對戰的都是真人嗎
So, are you playing with real people right now?
沒錯  來自全世界的玩家
Yeah. From all over the world.
來  你試試
Here, you try it.
-呀  我被吞了  -按這個鍵
- Oh, I got eaten. - Press that.
我明白了  我又變小了
Ah, oh, I see. It makes you small again.
對  你每次都得重頭開始
Yeah, you gotta start over from square one every single time.
我的天  我又被吞了
Oh, God. I got eaten again.
如果其他玩家知道對手是什么人
I wonder what the other players would think
不知道會怎么想
if they knew who they were playing against.
我倒挺喜歡匿名的
Oh, I'm rather enjoying the anonymity.
這真是史無前例
This is unprecedented.
誰是第一夫人  克萊爾·安德伍德還是凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
總統和康威州長
The president and Governor Conway
正在大會會場舉行閉門會談
are meeting right now at the convention hall.
兩名候選人面對面
Two candidates, face to face.
他們已經進去十分鐘了
They've been in there for about ten minutes,
據說在討論如何應對哈里發國問題
supposedly discussing the ICO situation.
而兩名總統候選人繼續進行
Now, while the private meeting between the two candidates
閉門會談的同時
continues behind closed doors,
場內代表們正在
delegates on the floor
準備進行下一輪投票
are gearing up for the next round of voting for...
我們得下去了  下一輪投票馬上就要開始了
We should head down. The next ballot is starting soon.
-我馬上就去  -在第二輪投票中
- I'll be down in a minute. - In the second round of voting
四分之一的代表改變了選擇
a quarter of the delegates changed their votes,
第三輪投票即將開始
第一夫人成副總統候選人有力競爭者
第二輪投票結果
杜蘭特
安德伍德
支持第一夫人安德伍德的呼聲越來越高
support for First Lady Claire Underwood is picking up steam,
這要部分歸功于今天的頭條新聞
thanks in part to today's breaking story
稱安德伍德夫人在勃蘭登堡會談中立下大功
about Mrs. Underwood's involvement in the Brandenburg negotiations.
參議員斯考特·希爾投下的一張支持票
A single vote from Senator Scott Sheer
擴展到整個德州代表團轉而支持第一夫人
expanded to support from the entire Texas delegation.
你好像  有個電話
You've, uh, got a call.
我最好接下  肯定是大事  他們才會打給我
Yeah, I better take that. They only call if it's important.
我是威爾
Yeah, this is Will.
好  轉接過來吧
Yes, put it through.
-失陪  -沒事
- Um, excuse me. - Sure.
說吧
Go ahead.
可惡  什么都聽不到
Damn! Nothing.
這是戰爭迷霧
The fog of war.
密室里的密室
A back room within a back room.
不管他在里面搞什么陰謀
Whatever's being plotted in there,
肯定對我不利
I can tell you it's no good for me.
每到這種時候我都巴不得是尼克松
You know, it's at times like these I wish I was Nixon,
嚴密監聽著每一個角落
had every nook and cranny bugged.
-總統先生  -你那個同事
- Mr. President? - Your colleague.
他的定向性有多高
How targeted can he get?
我們實在不該在電話里討論這些事
We really shouldn't be discussing this over the phone.
他能單獨針對一個人嗎
Can he isolate a specific person?
技術上講可以  但是
Technically, yes, but--
一段特定的對話呢
A conversation?
程序中有專門防止這么做的閉鎖機制
There are catch mechanisms in the program to prevent that.
他可以進行破解  但會留下痕跡
He can override, but it leaves a trail.
他還在研究如何掩蓋痕跡
He's still figuring out how to mask it.
我們紐約來的朋友
Our friend from New York.
我想知道他現在正在說什么
I want to know what he's saying right now.
先生  我表示強烈反對
Sir, I strongly advise against that.
我也建議我們掛電話
I also advise that we hang up.
好吧  我掛了
All right, I'm hanging up.
州長  我們該出去了吧
Governor, should we head out?
馬上  總統先生
Just a moment, Mr. President.
目前對于亞特蘭大有很大期待...
There's a great deal of anticipation in Atlanta...
誰打來的
Who was that?
總統  他想知道最新的代表投票數
The president. He just wanted the latest delegate count.
...下一輪投票還有幾分鐘就開始了
...and we're minutes away from the next ballot.
這是昨天上一輪投票的圖表
Here's a graphic of the last round yesterday.
國務卿凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
Secretary Catherine Durant
以22%的代表票數領先
led the way with 22% of delegates.
道格很不高興
Doug hates it.
他不高興什么
He hates what?
你可以直接接觸總統
That you have direct access to the president
不用通過他
without going through him.
他希望你走人
He wants you gone.
道格這么跟你說的
Doug told you that?
他要我找你的把柄
He wants me to dig something up on you.
我還沒找到
I haven't found anything yet.
你不會找到的  因為我沒有把柄
And you won't, because there isn't anything.
我知道  否則我現在已經找到了
I know. Otherwise, I would've found it by now.
你為什么要跟我說這個
Why are you telling me this?
因為如果不是你走  我做不到  我就得走
Because either you're gone or I am, if I don't deliver.
除非你給我點什么
Unless you give me something.
第一夫人克萊爾·安德伍德
...First Lady Claire Underwood,
驚人地出現在第五位
a surprising fifth place show...
可以是個小把柄  沒什么大危害的
It can be small. Nothing too damaging.
只要讓我有東西給他看
Just so I have something to show him.
在我報道總統選舉的三十年職業生涯中
In my 30 years of covering presidential politics,
從未見過這樣的事
I've never seen anything like it.
不好意思
Sorry about that.
沒關系
That's all right.
我們出去吧  下輪投票馬上要開始了
Shall we go out? The next ballot is about to start.
你想一起看嗎
You want to watch it together?
我們在這里待得越久  看起來越好
It might look better, the longer we're in here.
就像我們為美國的未來搏斗了一番似的
Like we grappled with the future of America.
除非你想出去跟群眾在一起
Unless you'd rather be out there with the masses.
天吶  群眾們
Oh, Christ. The masses.
-我也是這么覺得  -我們現在開始
- I feel the same way. - We will now commence
為我們黨
the third ballot
副總統候選人提名進行第三輪投票
for the nomination of our party's vice presidential candidate.
我們從阿拉巴馬州開始
We will start with Alabama.
秘書長女士
Madam Secretary,
偉大的阿拉巴馬州
the great state of Alabama,
在美國副總統提名投票上
for Vice President of the United States,
將29票投給國務卿凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
casts 29 votes for Secretary Catherine Durant,
26票投給第一夫人克萊爾·安德伍德
26 votes for the First Lady Claire Underwood,
剩下的三票投給莫比爾市長
and our three remaining votes for the Mayor of Mobile,
阿拉巴馬州的簡·溫斯洛普
Alabama's own Jane Winthrop.
紅潮[阿拉巴馬球隊]威猛
Roll Tide!
阿拉斯加州  接下來是你們
Alaska, you're next.
八票投給國務卿杜蘭特
Eight votes for Secretary of State Durant,
六票投給約瑟夫·貝克參議員
six votes for Senator Joseph Baker,
四票投給第一夫人克萊爾·安德伍德
four votes for First Lady Claire Underwood.
加利福尼亞州
California,
你們有476票
you have 476 votes.
233票投給凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
Two hundred and thirty-three for Catherine Durant,
152票投給約瑟夫·貝克
152 for Joseph Baker,
91票投給克萊爾·安德伍德
91 for Claire Underwood.
那對第一夫人是極大的支持
That's huge for the First Lady.
讓她上升到第三位  并逼近第二位
That puts her in third, and she's closing in on second.
特拉華州
Delaware.
12票給杜蘭特
Twelve for Durant,
11票給克萊爾·安德伍德
11 for Claire Underwood,
4票給貝克
four for Baker.
夏威夷州  接下來是你們
Hawaii, you're next.
17票投給第一夫人
Seventeen for the First Lady,
14票投給國務卿凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
and 14 for Secretary of State Catherine Durant.
她真的有機會
She's got a real shot.
難以置信
Unbelievable!
也沒有那么難以置信
Well, not so unbelievable.
44票投給凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
Forty-four votes for Catherine Durant,
35票投給克萊爾·安德伍德
35 votes for Claire Underwood.
路易斯安那州
Louisiana,
你們有61票
you have 61 votes.
你們怎么投
How do you cast them?
秘書長女士
Madam Secretary...
路易斯安那州把61票投給國務卿凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
Louisiana casts its 61 votes for President of the United States
競選美國總統
to Secretary of State Catherine Durant.
路易斯安那州  你想說的是副總統吧
Louisiana, I assume you mean vice president.
我說的就是總統
I mean president.
秘書長女士  路易斯安那州
Madam Secretary, the state of Louisiana
認為這次大會應該向
believes this convention should be open
所有位置開放  包括總統
for all parts of the ticket, including president.
路易斯安那州
Louisiana!
正如大會昨天上午達成的共識
As the convention agreed to yesterday morning,
我們會先選出副總統候選人
we are taking vice presidential nominations first,
以在整個大會上進行那一程序
in order for that process to take place over the full convention.
我們只有一位總統候選人
We have one candidate for president.
任何關于該項投票的討論
Any further discussion on that balloting
將放在副總統提名程序
will be taken up after the vice presidential nomination process
完成之后
is complete.
如果你不把票投出去的話  視為棄權
If you do not cast your votes, you will forfeit them.
秘書長女士  我們路易斯安那州
Madam Secretary, we, Louisiana,
把副總統提名的61票
cast our 61 votes for vice president,
還是投給凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
also for Catherine Durant.
路易斯安那州
Louisiana.
我在他手下干  是他的內閣成員
I work for the man. I'm on his cabinet.
如果總統提名公開競選  你會同他競爭嗎
Would you run against him if his nomination were in play?
我的目標是和總統一起參選  而非互相競爭
My goal is to run with the president, not against him.
聽著  我愛我的家鄉  路易斯安那
Look, I love my home state of Louisiana,
-但他們太熱情  -她會勝任的
- but they're a live bunch... - She'd do a good job.
不過她做國務卿會更出色
She's a much better Secretary of State, though.
我相信事情最終會得到解決的
I'm confident this will all work itself out.
我考慮過你敗選之后保留她的位置
I've considered keeping her on after you lose.
你有沒有就他們的倒戈與安德伍德總統溝通過
Have you spoken to President Underwood about their defection?
還沒有  但我想我很快就會與他談話的
Not yet, but I'll be speaking with him shortly, I imagine.
不過大會的意義...
Hey, this is part of what a...
-你那通電話  -就在于此
- Your call.  - ...convention is all about.
我也想能居功  但是她找的我
I wish I could take credit, but... but she called me.
不過說回來  當機會到來的時候
Then again, when opportunity strikes...
非常感謝
Thank you very much.
這絕對不算贏得有尊嚴
Definitely not the way to win with dignity.
杜蘭特就她的家鄉路易斯安那發表評論
...Durant commenting on her home state of Louisiana.
如果你能贏的話
If you win at all.
我們該出去了
We should get back out there.
你還得爭取提名呢
You've got a nomination to fight for.
總統和我的談話非常順利
The president and I, we had a great talk.
我們甚至還一起觀看了投票
We, uh, even watched the vote together.
但是我想你們肯定更想聽他怎么說
But I'm sure you'd rather hear from him on that than me.
謝謝  州長
Well, thank you, Governor.
今天還真是充滿意外  不是嗎
Today has certainly been full of surprises, hasn't it?
但是話說回來
But, then again,
畢竟休伊·朗就來自路易斯安那州
Louisiana is the state that gave us Huey Long after all.
該州前州長
政績出色  競選總統時遇刺
雖然我很想討論這個話題
As much as I would like to discuss this,
但是我必須著手開始處理
I have to get on with the business
州長和我剛剛探討的那些問題
that the governor and I have just discussed,
因為當總統比競選總統重要得多
because the business of the presidency trumps running for it.
-謝謝  州長  -謝謝  總統先生
- Thank you, Governor.  - Thank you, Mr. President.
非常感謝各位
Thank you all very much.
我很愿意回答
I'm happy to answer...
馬上把凱茜叫到我房間
I want Cathy in my room, now.
我已經給她打過電話了  她拒絕會面
I already called her. She refuses to meet.
-她什么  -她就是這么說的
- She what?  - That's what she said,
然后她就把電話掛了
and then she hung up.
她的手下也不回我電話
Her staff won't return my calls either.
這事想辦成  你必須回華盛頓去
For this to work, you have to go back to Washington.
我不能拋下你一個人處理這件事
I can't leave while you're dealing with this.
如果你留下的話  大家會覺得你在從中漁利
If you stay, it will look like you're taking advantage
并且真的在參選
and campaigning for it.
而這件事的關鍵就在于讓人覺得你沒這意思
And the key is to make it look like you're not.
我會找凱茜談的
I'll speak with Cathy.
不用  我已經在處理了
No, look, I've got that covered.
問題是我們怎么解釋你的離開
Question is, how we justify your going.
不去華盛頓
It's not Washington.
應該去德州
It should be Texas.
-你母親  -上次就好使
- Your mother.  - It worked before.
我明天一早就走
I'll leave first thing in the morning.
帶上湯姆一起
Take Tom with you.
-湯姆  -他已經知道了
- Tom?  - Oh, he already knows.
-你告訴他了嗎  -他自己猜出來了
- Did you tell him?  - He put it together.
他說  如果你能贏下來的話
He said, if you win this thing...
你必須做一次空前絕后的講話  他說得對
you have to give the speech of a lifetime, and he's right.
不管你在大會堂里說什么
Whatever you say in that convention hall
都會給我們把你推向全國
will lay the groundwork for how we sell this
打下基礎
to the rest of the country.
而這就是我們叫他回來的原因  對吧
And that is why we brought him back, right?
你能坐著就睡著嗎
You can sleep like that? Sitting up?
我在哪都能睡著
I can sleep anywhere.
真挺有福的
I'm lucky like that.
我們有活兒要干
We have work to do.
好吧  那就干活兒
All right, let's work.
這段得改
This could be better.
對著我大聲讀出來
Read it for me. Out loud.
我在婚姻中做我丈夫的搭檔已有29年
I've been my husband's partner in marriage for 29 years.
不行
No.
慢點
Slower.
就像你在大會上講話那樣
Like you're going to say it at the convention.
我在婚姻中做我丈夫的搭檔已有29年
I've been my husband's partner in marriage for 29 years.
現在  到了我
Now, it's time for me to be..."
這樣我能看到你的臉
So I can see your face.
我在婚姻中做我丈夫的搭檔已有29年
I've been my husband's partner in marriage for 29 years.
現在到了我在接下來的4年中
Now, it's time for me to be his
進入白宮  繼續做他的搭檔的時候了
partner in the White House for the next four.
你說得對
You're right.
是得改
We can do better.
■
美國現有的總統選舉  尤其是黨內初選制度
是經過漫長的演化才最終形成的
初選選舉  選民所選出的并不是總統候選人
而是代表本州參加黨代會的代表
所以初選結果計算的并不是候選人獲得的選民票數
而是其贏得的州代表數  也就是"選舉人票"
這些代表在參加黨代會時  再投票決定本黨的提名人
■
19世紀時  各州黨內初選結果只是作為一種民意的評測
直到20世紀初  一些州才陸續規定將選舉結果同最終的提名掛鉤
20世紀60年代之前  民主黨  共和黨兩黨挑選提名人時
很大程度上依賴于黨代會召開期間
黨內大佬和候選人之間的私下談判和政治交易
1968年  民主黨候選人亨福瑞雖然沒有贏得任何一個州的初選
但仍靠黨代會上的交易成為了民主黨提名人
68年后  民主黨決定改革初選制度
使各州的初選結果成為決定提名人的主要途徑
共和黨隨后也對黨內初選制度做出了相應的改革
■
無論改革前還是改革后
兩黨都要求總統候選人必須獲得至少過半的選舉人票
若多名候選人參選  而沒有任何一個獲得過半的選舉人票
黨代會便成為了"開放黨代會"
各州代表需要在黨代會上進行一輪輪投票
直到某個候選人得到多數票為止
1924年的民主黨黨代會上
選民代表經過102輪投票才選出最終的提名人
上一次出現需要代表在黨代會上
反復投票決定提名人的情況是1952年
■
正在緊張進行的2016年大選中  共和黨陣營群雄爭霸
目前雖然地產大亨特朗普在選票上領先
但其他幾名候選人仍然十分具有競爭力
而且由于特朗普言行頗受爭議
許多共和黨內部人士認為  如果不能在選票上打敗特朗普
就要寄望于"開放黨代會"  通過州代表投票把特朗普選下來